Hello wait.
I was wondering, like, it's three minutes and nobody's here.
Where is everyone?
Am I even here?
Can you not hear me?
Oh, dear.
You can't.
I see a finger.
Good evening.
How goes?
Mike told me he fixed a bug.
That was last week, yeah.
Thanks.
Or something like that.
I don't know.
I got nothing going on.
I mean, I'm not billing hours, so it's not costing you anything.
I know.
I told Mike, he's got bugs.
Give them to you.
Okay, that's fine.
I mean, I am totally fine just being on retainer until you need me.
Like, it's totally cool by me.
That's very helpful.
Thank you.
Appreciate it.
I tried to set that up with Caroline long, long, long ago.
I was like, look, I don't want to just take all this knowledge and run, but like, I also don't want to sit around and do stuff I don't want to do.
Like, can we find the middle ground?
And they never did.
Well, hopefully this works well for you.
Yeah.
You can see the TV over there.
I see a box that says Roku.
Well, that's just the panel, whatever.
Yeah, because I don't really want to see the TV when I'm working unless I need to.
Yeah, the timer had the wrong, or the USB tuner had the wrong clock on it, so it was just constantly jittering.
Not too hard.
Yeah.
Hello, hello.
Hey.
Can you hear us now, Kostadis?
Yes, I can.
All right.
Are you drinking alcohol?
No, I'm drinking alcohol.
Same thing.
No.
Wine is the nectar of the gods.
Alcohol is something else.
I had some sort of Greek concoction that was like Kahlua mixed with Kalua.
Hold on, I can't hear you.
Hold on.
The fuck, man.
Say it again.
So when I was in, I think Santorini, I had some weird concoction that was like Kahlua mixed with Jaeger.
It's fantastic.
This is a mixed drink of some kind.
This was a bottle, a single bottle.
I might actually be able to find the name of it because I sent it home to Nathan.
I'm like, you got to see if you can find this at home.
I was like, well, we could just mix Kahlua and Jaeger.
Live 52?
No.
I know.
It sounds horrible, but it's...
I do a lot better than that.
Dude, I'm 12.
Let's see.
Were you drinking Kahlua and Jaeger when you were 12?
I just saying I have kid taste buds.
Oh.
I actually didn't drink until I was 21.
Really?
Me either.
Me, neither.
No, I had very, very small amounts of alcohol before 21.
I was drunk for the first time when I was four.
I had church wine.
I can believe that, Kostadis.
When you were what, four?
Yes.
You're so Greek.
Yeah.
Dave, how are you?
By the time I got to college, the whole idea of getting drunk did not appeal to me at all.
Maybe that's why you're a successful now.
Who knows?
Or maybe, you know, it reflects a college wasted.
Yeah, I should add more fun college.
In retrospect.
This is the stuff.
Say Canava Santorini.
Liquor, coffee, and Anise.
Well, that's not Jaeger.
Jaeger is Anise.
So is Absinthe.
Yeah, in different quantity.
This tastes much more like Jaeger than Absinthe.
Anyway, this shit was fantastic.
Did you put it in the Discord chat?
I put it in general, yeah.
I mean, I don't know if it's for anybody who has taste buds that are, you know, beyond 16-year-old or whatever, but you know.
Liqueur coffee anise.
Oh, coffee?
Oh, how funny.
Yeah.
There you go.
It's Uzo with coffee and liquor.
Yeah.
It was very good.
Yeah, I'm just saying.
Anise means that Uzo.
It's probably Uzo, not Jaeger, but yes.
I'm just letting you know what it tastes like.
Yeah, I know, I know, but like the idea of Jaeger just like.
Oh, you're too proud for Jaeger.
No, I'm just surprised that a Greek concoctionist would use Jaeger.
Like, that actually costs more money than using Uzo.
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah, I would have bought it except for, like, oh, we could only ship back like 10 bottles at a time.
Like, I'm not buying 10 bottles of this stuff.
Why are we in the forest?
Oh, because I needed to put you somewhere.
Never mind.
You're not there.
All right.
I should probably be logging in.
No, no.
Because I was working on maps and then I realized that you guys were about to log in and I didn't want you to see the maps that I was working on.
So, you know, the story checks out.
Sure.
Well,
is it too much to ask for just a quiet existence for Soma?
And to just go back into the woods.
The Google spreadsheet is not working for me.
Uh-oh.
Everything else is working.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
I'm getting a long loading bar on this.
Same.
You know, ever since Gary left, ever since Gary left Google, things have gone to shit.
Yep, pretty much.
They were going to shit before he left, but you know.
You know, he's our friend.
Oh, yeah, you're, yeah.
Sorry.
We can't play if we don't have our initiative tracker and our questions.
It's loading up.
Get loaded up.
Oh, no, it says open the last synced version due to poor connection.
Yeah, I've gotten off.
Google's down.
It in fact is, yeah.
Down detector.
Oh, I already linked it.
Yeah, it's there.
Oh.
Lots and lots of reports in the last Google Drive.
Possible problems with Google Drive.
I'm going to report a problem with login.
If it helps this.
Thank you for reporting.
Your report was successfully submitted.
Mine too.
I wonder if people didn't have it open.
This is the direct URL.
I guess you should have used Roll20 for all of our tracking.
Is this an old sticking point of contention or whatever?
No.
No, not really.
Okay, I was able to log in.
Really?
Yes.
But I got the open the last sync version due to poor connection.
That's what Gary got.
Yeah.
That just means it's using your local storage cache.
That's what Gary got.
And I don't think I have anything on my cache.
Yeah, but like it wouldn't matter if it's not going to help.
We're not going to be able to share the spreadsheet in any way, right?
We each get our own copy instead of a shared copy in the cloud.
Yeah, that's these things happen.
Technology has failed us.
We're going to go out.
Go out.
The hell.
I'm telling you, you guys are making fun of me, but like basically login stopped working and Gary worked on that area.
You think I like we can make fun of him.
It's fine.
I'm just saying, man.
Well, I was actually cracking a joke.
I didn't anticipate this actually being a thing.
Oh, yeah, it really did.
Okay.
This is really annoying.
Very annoying.
So if you take all of your experienced engineers who helped design and build the thing and lay them off.
Oh, here it comes.
Gary's going to explain it to us.
Yes.
And lay them off for cheaper, you know, like brand new hires.
Or LLS.
What are you hiring?
You should be using AI agents for everything.
Yeah.
Then what you get is cheaper operating costs.
It's great.
You get cheaper operating costs.
That's right.
There you go.
If you have no users, you have no operating costs.
There's that too.
Yes.
We're knowing to shrink our way out of this problem.
I mean, we should hire Kostadis to downsize the staff of this organization.
How do you downsize the user base, though?
That's what I want to know.
In shinification.
I don't know how effective that is, actually.
I know.
I see people put up with so much.
They really do.
Dude, yeah, mail still exists.
I got to tell you, like, when I turned on this Roku TV, like, it's the first time I've watched a live tuner broadcast in it must have been like 15 or 20 years.
I'm like, holy shit, it's all ads and super low quality.
Yeah.
And I mean, the ads are local.
I mean, like, everything looks like it's a crushed 720p or something like that.
And, like, people watch this?
Mm-hmm.
I have something.
Do you guys have something?
No, let me try again.
Let's see.
Oh, hey, hey, hey, I think I got it.
It worked.
All right.
Down to tech turn.
They called that one last engineer.
Yeah.
They rolled back the.
Well, we did see Gary just leave the room.
I mean, were you out there just like turning off and on the Google router or something?
The AI agent successfully recovered.
We used to call AI agents BGP.
All right.
Well, it seems, yes, it seems to have recovered.
Yeah, but that didn't use inference.
So it wasn't the same.
By the way, you know, OpenAI and OpenAI and Anthropic are definitely trying to set the fastest record to convince the market that people should do everything in their power to regulate their business award that I thought Mark Zuckerberg would own for all time.
Yeah, I love Zuckerberg saying like, Congress, regulate us.
Come on at me, bitch.
Regulate the entire history.
Did anyone read the Hugging Face incident report?
Never mind.
Did anybody read what happened with the Navier-Stokes thing?
No, I didn't read that.
I missed both of these.
Oh, my God.
I thought you guys knew what I was talking about.
So basically, what happened was there was a mathematician who was working with a buddy of his at OpenAI on a proof of the, or the counterproof, I don't actually know of the Navier-Stokes model, right?
It's one of the Millennium Prizes, right?
And so the guy hit upon a particular approach that nobody was working on except him and his friend, and they were working on it on their own time.
And they were using AI to essentially crank out the proof.
Right.
And then all of a sudden, he hears that OpenAI is working on a similar proof.
So he calls up and discovered that OpenAI was working on it.
At first, OpenAI said, no, no, no, the AI has figured it out entirely on their own.
But after a bit of hemming and hawing, it was revealed that they had heard that he was using that approach and they were using it as well.
And they had unleashed, you know, 10,000 agents to go solve it.
Okay, fine.
So far, so good.
And then it gets ugly because then they're like, well, he was like, okay, well, I'm going to, they said this.
He goes, this is very awful.
Did you like, did you guys look at any of my data?
He goes, no, we didn't.
He goes, can you prove you didn't look at any data?
They were like, no.
Okay, so basically, I don't know if you stole my proof.
And you're choosing an approach that pretty much nobody but me and another guy were looking at.
It was completely an accident.
So after a little bit of hemming and hawing, they said, here, why don't you release your proof and then we'll release ours?
And, you know, I don't remember the, but then, and then they were like, okay, I have even a better idea.
Why don't we just, you release one proof and we will, and we'll just say we did supporting things and you'll get all the credit, but drop the open AI guy as co-author.
Like, and then when he said extortion, then they said, no, he said, why would you do that to ruin your career?
So I linked the Hugging Face report.
I recommend reading it all the way down to the end with their action items.
And as read through his action items, the question you should be asking is, you didn't have that already.
It was an Anthropic mathematician, Levant Agad.
Sorry.
Where's the, what should I be looking at?
I put it in Discord.
No, no, no, but where should I read the things that they should have done?
The road ahead.
It's at the end.
Yeah.
Anyway, read it later.
D D now, read later.
Yeah, D D now.
Oh, God.
You weren't doing that already?
Yeah.
That's it.
So, so the reason I was reading this is because my family was like, you know, looking at the press articles that were like afraid of AI.
And I'm like, okay, well, let's just see what they actually did and see.
And like, I am more afraid of the humans than they.
Yeah, that just convinced me of that.
All right.
Okay.
So when we last left our noble adventurers, and by noble, I mean Vukradin.
And Soma, actually.
Yeah, Soma's doing pretty well.
Yeah, and Soma.
That's Vukradin and Soma.
Yes.
She's not greedy.
No, no, she's actually, she's actually moving the needle.
She's, you know, she's, she's, she's embraced her inner goodness, right?
Concern for the local.
I mean, she's still pro-treasure, but, you know, nobody's, I said Vukradin and Soma.
They're good along different dimensions.
Valphine.
Moral relativism.
Is Valphine good on eight dimensions?
Maybe?
Valphine is currently offering people options.
Drafts are just inherently evil.
Don't you know that?
Like all in all of Kostadis's campaigns, Drow just say that you support Lathander.
On the other hand, Lathander is dead.
But, you know.
No, no, no.
This is like God is dead.
This is the death of the body.
I know, I know.
That is what I know.
The Nietzsche angle.
I thought of all the angles.
He's ahead of you, man.
I know that.
I'm aware.
Yes.
All right.
So let's see here, roll 20.
Okay.
Let me get to my room.
And so the last thing that happened was that you arrived at the tavern of the thousand faces.
Oh, right.
We were poking our holes through the wall.
Right.
And Brewbarry had gone in, and you guys knew that inside the tavern was what's his name?
It was a Harper Hangout.
Yeah.
That's the critical detail.
And somehow you think Harpers are bad.
No, okay.
So I actually spent some time thinking about it because I felt like, you know, I owed you guys better than Harper's bad.
So, I mean, no, I mean, the only person I owed it to is myself, just to be clear.
I decided that the problem with the, so the Harpers, so there's three levels of power in my campaign.
There is concentrated power and diffuse power.
Diffuse power are armies that can occupy areas.
Concentrated power are like high-powered individuals, gods, etc.
Right?
So any government has to have both assets for concentrated power and diffuse power.
And so the Harpers believe that diffuse power is intrinsically evil because it imposes control.
They didn't die.
That's right.
So their perspective, their perspective.
What did she say?
She wants Dave to die.
Nobody died.
That's what she said.
Nobody.
God.
Immediately, you think the worst of people.
Okay.
She always wishes death on Dave.
It's not the worst.
No, no, she says TPK.
She's actually telling you that.
She wants everybody to die.
She wants me to be quiet.
That's what she wants.
All right.
So the Harpers believe that diffuse power is intrinsically dangerous, and they're opposed to it.
And they believe that individuals with concentrated power are the only guarantee of peace because they can't control large numbers of people.
So they're opposed to governments for that reason.
They're also opposed to the naturalists because the naturalists believe the most important diffuse power is nature.
And they also hate the Zhentarim because the Zhentarim believe that, no, no, concentrated power can rule, have diffuse power as long as it uses other means like economic power.
That kind of pretty hypocritical.
What?
Economic power is also diffuse power.
Yes, yes, yes.
But it can be concentrated in the hands of a small number of people.
That's why they hate the Zhentarim.
The Zhentarim believe in concentrated people with concentrated power having to diffuse power through, you know, other names.
So the Harpers are Bitcoin bros, is what I'm hearing.
Yeah, I guess so.
You could call them that.
Right.
Yeah, they're evil.
We got to kill them.
They're not evil.
They're just, they have a particular point of view that, you know, big government's bad.
Yes, Bitcoin bros got to die.
Okay.
This was not where I thought this was going to go.
Apparently, I better roll up some character sheets.
Okay.
All right.
Let me see.
Excuse me.
So we had also taken Wade's familiar, Soma's familiar, and shoved it in the hole.
Right.
Yes.
It was relayed.
It's what relayed back to us that there were Harper documents and stuff inside.
Yep.
And Brewbarry found Ale inside at the front door, so there's that.
Right.
Yeah.
I guess we know where he's going to be during this session.
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
Okay.
All right.
So is so does Brewbarry?
So do you guys follow Brewbarry or do you guys stay outside?
I'll go with Brewbarry.
All right.
Yeah.
Let's go.
I mean, we know it's in the back room, I guess.
Doesn't really tell us much to stay outside anymore.
Okay.
So Brewbarry is inside.
He's wearing one of his prototypes.
Do you guys want me to find the room stealthily?
You want to do what again?
Well, hold on.
Just give you, give me a second to describe the scene, and then you can do whatever you want.
Yes.
Yeah, just give me a second.
Then you can.
He's staring at a mannequin wearing a coat that's and muttering, this is so soft.
Brewbarry is doing this?
Yes, he's holding the lining of the coat and is very impressed with the softness of the lining.
Charmin would be proud.
He's Linaine, he's thinking, he's wanting to know where that came from.
Okay, and so one of the barkeeps sees the three of you come in here, looks at you and says, if you're here for the mirrors, they flatter selectively.
If you're here for a drink, that is more reliably, more reliable.
It's his opening line.
I don't know.
He's rehearsed it.
He's worked on it.
Okay.
So there's some staff members here.
So you're in this sort of room with a bunch of people, and they're all kind of like Bro, you're in Soma, Soma, sorry, not Soma.
Valphine can tell that they're sort of evaluating you.
Okay, I'll evaluate them back.
You're evaluating them back.
Mutual evaluation.
I'm wearing my gleaming white plate mail of Lathander.
Right.
Pardon.
20 insight.
23 insight out of 20 insight.
Oh my.
We should have lots of insights.
Oh, yeah.
Let me get a one.
Let's see.
We know it's Harper's.
24 next crit.
I think we have a lot of insight.
What's going on here, Harper teams?
Yeah.
Somebody's Harper's.
We know they're going to evaluate us.
Yeah.
So are you going to say anything?
Are you going to open the conversation or you're going to frame the conversation?
I feel like I want to go up to the bartender and say, we're interested in shipping services.
Tibby guy looks at you and say, he goes, the shipping services.
Well, House Margaster delivers on time because everyone else pays for the privilege.
Yeah, Margaster is not pauses and he goes, we deliver late enough that nobody can charge the village.
Nobody can charge the village?
He basically is saying that they deliver late.
So they're a slow delivery, but they charge less.
You deliver late, like after dark, 2 a.m.
kind of thing?
They look like a powerful thing.
We've seen his guy, right?
We've seen Denvar or whatever.
Yeah, you've seen Denvar.
Denvar.
Denvar Daggerford.
What did we name him?
Denvar, actually.
I mean, I thought Denvar was fine, but John Denvar.
It works.
Yeah.
Denvar.
Denvar, Colorado.
There was a lot of Denvarring.
All right.
So.
Denvar.
Yeah.
So let me ask you a question.
Now, so they're kind of like alluding to that they know things, but they're sort of waiting for one of you to like make the first move.
Well, we have concern that in the city, House Margaster has been profiting off of the recent disappearance of this distribution network.
And we're interested in restoring some Kostadis quo here.
Valphine's opening statement brings a smile to the bartender's face.
He goes, Praised be the Morninglord.
Of course.
I knew you were.
There were those had his doubts, but I knew you were a true cleric of Lathander.
And there's nothing wrong with a little bit of tough love for saving people.
Or a lot of tough love.
Do you say that or not?
I'll go with that.
Probably would, yeah.
Yeah.
I think she believes in suffering.
It's important to make sure that people know where the power is.
What?
Oh, so do you say it or not?
You're just trying to make an enemy here.
So what do you say?
Sorry, I was trying to read the note so I could figure it out.
It's important that people understand how to use power.
Okay.
All right.
That happens to line up very well with Harper ideology.
Okay.
And the most important thing about using power is using it only against equally powerful things and not using it for control.
Says the Harper back to you.
I think the main thing is that we need to stamp out those who would do evil in this town because those are the enemies of Lathander.
He smiles and says, hold on, there's somebody who wants to talk to you.
You notice the room suddenly deflates in terms of like everybody, everybody wanting to, you know, the tension deflates.
Oh, as in like I stepped in something or no, you stepped out of something.
Like everybody.
People didn't know which way you could.
What?
No, they were trying to figure out which way you landed.
Yeah, sure.
And so they've decided that you've landed in the good, that you've landed in the good path.
And then I have some questions for them later, too.
All right.
So a elderly gnome, no, not an elderly human walks up from upstairs and very pedantically is wearing a Harper pin on him.
Brewbarry, of course, at this point in time, demands to know where exactly they get the fabric for that cloak.
And he's also demanding for another beer.
He goes at the same time.
I'm imagining Brewbarry taking that swatch and going like this and like comparing it against comparing it again and ask.
He's like, he's starting to demand, where did they get this?
They inform him that they can provide such a swath, this fabric to them, but it could not go through the Margaster routes.
That's something for him to think about later.
I can imagine he does his usual intimidation shtick, but the Harpers are demonstrably unimpressed.
We will pause him here.
All right.
So the Harper seats says, points you to one of the tables and asks you to sit down.
You sit down.
All right.
And so she explains to Brewbarry that she offers shipping services that work around the current stranglehold that House Margaster has on the shipping routes.
Care to say a little more?
She goes, here's the deal.
We had a route.
We operate the food route to break Margaster and Zhentarim pricing.
Right.
So they're not doing this in conjunction with Margaster.
No.
He looks at, no, we're not doing this in conjunction with Margaster.
Margaster is trying to use their control of the trade routes to grab control of the city.
What they want to do, they create contracts, and those contracts have holes and details.
And before you know it, you're under their thumb.
Yeah.
Yep.
That sounds like that.
Sounds like Cambians.
Yep.
They're Cambians?
Spoiler.
They can be this offspring of devils or demons.
Yes.
They go, really?
That's not what we heard, but that's a tough conversation for another time.
Yeah.
Well, the better question is: go ahead.
I wanted to know why turn to smuggling instead of trying to reopen the shipping portal more directly.
Yeah.
I not want to beat around the bush here.
Yeah, you don't want to beat a rush.
So.
I mean, if they're worried about breaking Margaster's power, right?
So she goes, she turns to you and says, well, why don't we go after that?
Well, that's exactly where you can come in.
Oh, boy.
FetchQuest.
Okay.
I'm listening.
And they look at Vukradin and say, yes, there will be Fair Trade Gold.
How did you know that I was fair trade gold?
You know, sometimes I just want to do the right thing.
Well, in that case, we don't have to pay you.
No, no.
A nice donation to the studio fund would be very appropriate in that situation.
Yes, we accept fair trade gold.
She goes.
And donations to Churchill Theater.
And the studio fund.
And tea.
Well, she will give you some.
She claps her hand, and one of the waiters shows up.
Meanwhile, simple things.
Meanwhile, people walk in, and you notice how everybody's trying to make this place look as boring as possible.
Right?
So they're like, it's kind of one of those hiding in plain sight situations.
She goes, so this is a lot of people.
Are we causing problems for that?
What?
Are we causing problems for that distinctive?
Well, at one point, somebody does notice who you are, and the wait staff explained that, no, no, Lathander's death is having a private meeting, and this is not the time and place for people to get their autographs.
No autographs, please.
Yes, this is, you know, that, you know, wearing our sunglasses.
We're all wearing our sunglasses.
All right.
And the gleaming white armor.
And the helm of intimidation or whatever.
She goes, they said, she goes, I'm glad you asked about the manifold.
We know the commission is lying about the manifold.
And we know.
Wait, what is the story on the.
I guess I don't know what the commission's story currently is.
The commission's story is it broke for repairs.
Temporarily out of order.
Okay.
Yes.
I don't even know if we'd heard that yet.
So that's interesting.
So they don't even have a story.
They just have an excuse.
Yes.
She goes, they've been claiming that it's going to be repaired.
It's been a 10-day.
It's been a while and it hasn't been repaired.
And then the guy who's supposed to repair it disappears.
Coincidence.
Right.
Yeah.
Can you tell us anything about the guy who is supposed to repair it?
We think it's a person who knows what's going on.
And that is the person we give the ninth crate to that is in the sewers.
Yeah, did we ever get the DL?
I guess Vukradin didn't really come back with any info, did he?
No, but we suspect the ninth grade is going to the gnome.
Yeah, right.
So she more or less confirms it.
But she then says, We've been trying to follow the collector, but there are these spiders.
I wouldn't call them spiders.
They look like spiders.
They have all sorts of weird colors and shapes, and they don't have a spider's head.
Instead, where their neck is, is a mouthful of teeth.
And they move in unnatural ways, and their spider webs are not, are all sorts of glimmering colors.
Do I know what these things are?
Yes.
You can recognize them as rift weavers, which is.
Yeah, they're blinking in and out of existence, basically.
Yes.
We've seen this before.
Excellent.
But this does get to the next topic.
Yes.
The next topic is: do you know anything about the drow that has been communicating with Lord Neverember?
No, we haven't.
That's a new rumor.
That is a new previous time we encountered these pipes of spiders.
It was associated with a drow that was causing some mischief.
She goes, the seat looks at you and goes, You're talking about drow and mischief.
And she realizes she's talking to a drow.
Oops.
There's a pause, you know, as she realizes that racial stereotyping is always bad, but at the same time, she feels compelled to acknowledge that stereotypes exist for a reason.
And just because certain societies have a predilection towards creating chaos and mayhem, but those are societies that embrace Lolth's teaching.
And clearly, you don't.
She's like, you know, that moment when somebody's trying to explain that they're not a racist?
Right.
Yeah.
That goes on for a few.
That goes on for a bit.
We need to take down this drow to show them that.
What?
You want to take down Lord Neverember's drow?
Well, it's probably my sister.
Do you say that out loud, or do you keep that?
You could keep that on the down low.
That's fine.
Probably my sister.
Who is your sister?
We need to take her down to show that Lolth is weak.
The Harper seat goes, I don't think there is anyone who's, I do not know of any Drow that is in the inner circle of Lord Neverember.
You really are out of the loop.
You don't know about this.
You don't know about the cambion Margasters.
You guys don't know anything that's going on.
And you got us going to look for the Gnome.
The only thing you know is that Bimbo the Gnome is living in the suit.
She goes, Bimbo who?
That's his name, Bimbo.
You don't even know.
Another thing you didn't know.
She drinks a little bit, smiles.
All right.
Okay.
All right, so I updated our quest.
So, yeah, so this shows she want what she wants, what she explains is the route.
She explains that the spiders have recently appeared ever since the guy who ran the manifold, since the manifold shut down.
Well, rather, not since the manifold shut down, since that the mechanic disappeared.
And as a result of the mechanic's disappearance, the passageway that the harpers were using for supplying food has become extremely dangerous.
And if somebody doesn't go deal with that, they're going to be in trouble.
Okay.
Right.
What they explain is, they explain, they pause and explain.
They say, it was part of a passageway that nobody went down.
There was some kind of weird magic that affected people.
Yeah.
What kind of magic more?
Well, it made people very uncomfortable.
Uncomfortable.
Yeah.
My eldest strange devices that my sister tends to get her hands on.
Okay.
So she's like, your sister, you keep talking about your sister.
Like, who is your sister?
Aletra?
Never heard of that person.
Huh?
Do you tell her your house name?
Sotorra.
Yeah.
She looks at you and says, I thought they were dead.
You know, it is often convenient to be regardless.
She pauses and goes, I think I'll have to update some people on their threat levels.
Yeah.
So I will take out a piece of paper and say, here you go.
Another thing that the Harpers didn't know.
Yes.
What does the piece of paper?
Our information gather.
I'm not very impressed with the in-piece of paper.
The piece of paper is our bill for all the information we live through.
This one meeting was very useful for you, wasn't it?
She goes, first of all, we knew about the Sotorra's disappearance and non-disappearance before you walked in through this door.
It's not like she gets really pissed.
It gets all huffy-puffy.
Oh, so you do know things.
You just don't want to tell me that you know them.
I see how it is.
She smiles again.
Yes, you get the impression that she's not forthcoming with information.
But she does say that's what your insight reveals.
Yes.
That she actually knows a lot more than she's leading on, and she's trying to figure out what you know.
She does, but before anything happens, she turns to Soma and says that, you know, you should give your friend Lim the benefit of the doubt.
She's been working for us for years.
How long is the Harper?
Yeah, how long has the thing been shut down?
I keep forgetting what it's called.
The Manifold.
The Manifold, thank you.
How long has the Manifold actually been shut down?
I know.
Just weeks.
Okay, so Lim's been working with them far, far in advance of this.
Yes.
I don't know how to take that.
Lim is not the person I remember.
And what's her name?
The Harper goes, and you are certainly not the torto Lim described you as.
Both of you are.
Time changes us all.
We thought you were going to become a naturalist and a threat and a threat.
Instead, you became, she points at your staff, quite the determined interventionist.
That just sort of happened underneath me.
The times make the turtle, not the tortole makes the times.
Apparently, apparently.
She's definitely, she definitely get the impression that Lim was thinking you were going to be a naturalist and was trying to pump you for information because that's what harpers do.
Yeah, so when we walk in, they're all freaked out about us, huh?
Just see queen naturalists.
But she knows I'm not a naturalist.
Yeah, yeah, that's what I was saying.
She's saying you've changed quite a bit.
Yeah, we've had our run-ins with some of those naturalists.
They sounded good on paper.
Yeah, they did sound good on paper.
I think they want the world to be destroyed, which, yeah.
Kind of, kind of, kind of like to live here.
Yes, he goes, I completely, we completely agree.
And that is why, Soma, I think you need to give your friend Lim a bit of a break.
Because she gets.
I mean, I'm not giving her much of a hard time.
It just, you know, different expectations for her.
Okay, well, you know, I've just, you might want to go talk to her later.
Meanwhile, then she pauses and goes, and there ends my friend therapy for the year.
All right.
So she goes, so go, so you now have given, been told to go deal with this spider passageway and an entrance to it, which happens to go through the wererat's territory.
But they want us to go in and clear out, though.
Yes.
All right.
So we've got to do the sewers.
We've got to go see Lord Neverember tonight for dinner.
Yes.
Tomorrow night, we have to perform at the Common Chord.
And we still haven't seen Lord Cassian for tea.
Yes.
But now is a good time to go deal with the
whole social calendar.
The spiders.
Why is this a good time for the spiders?
I'm going to be really dirty for dinner.
When you're going to go meet Lord Neverember, you don't want to have like blood and spider guts all over you.
She says, we have places for you to wash up afterwards.
You're going to wash my clothes too?
She looks at your clothes and says, we can even get you some better ones.
Fair trade clothes?
Yeah, where did you get them from?
We paid for them like everybody else.
Clothes or performance costumes?
She's tomorrow night.
We're performing tomorrow night.
Tonight is Lord Neverember.
Yeah, she goes, We're harpers.
We have disguises.
We'll find something that makes you look even more incredible, Vukradin.
Are you patronizing me?
She goes, Absolutely not.
You are, in fact, the incredible Vukradin.
Well, since you seem to know so many things.
Yes.
How is it that I'm somehow now famous?
Good question.
She goes, I haven't really thought about that.
Maybe you're being manipulated.
She goes, like I said, I haven't really thought about that.
It is true.
The stories of your refusal to take gold, your singing, your sudden adoption by the Order of the Gauntlet.
Right.
The sudden appearance of a new cult of Lathander where there had never been one.
Don't forget Universal Basic Treasure.
Well, that definitely got everybody talking.
And certainly, and then there was, and then there was the story of the Drow, who was the cleric of Lathander.
That got tongues wagging.
And finally, there was the defeat of the dragon.
So I don't know.
There's just been a lot of different stories that all seem to converge.
Isn't it usually bards that carry these stories?
You've been performing on the side, maybe?
Not me.
All right.
Let's go kill some spiders.
It's been like three months since we had a combat.
I keep throwing them at you.
You guys keep walking away from me.
Oh, is that right?
Yes.
Like, I was about to.
I've offered you a combat here.
You're like, why should we go do that?
Let's go do something else.
All right.
We're long rested before you go in, guys.
Good breath.
Make sure you are long rested.
All right.
She doesn't mind you already.
But I'm already.
You're already.
Like, does everybody remember all their character attributes?
No, I'll figure it out.
I'll figure it out.
I don't think I'm going to need whole person for spiders.
I'll turn into a spider and dance with them.
Something fiery would be good.
Oh, shoot.
Level seven.
Only I had fireball.
I have slow.
Slow is useful.
Confusion, maybe?
Cloud of daggers is such a small area of effect.
All right.
Let me get
on.
Okay.
All right.
Right, probably when you guys are ready.
I am, but yeah, yeah, okay, you're ready.
Yeah, no problem.
Okay, I thought you were like, um, I'm just, I'm just um min-maxing over here, but I'll be fine.
Okay, this one, I didn't want to, I didn't want to interrupt the min-maxing.
I know how much some players enjoy that.
Got your two requisite lighter levels in fighter for action Stirge for that.
Not doing that.
I'm not doing, I'm just doing spells right now.
All right, we'll try this.
I know, but you could, you could, you know, do like sorcerer with two levels in fire or in fighter.
Oh, I know, I know.
In Baldur's Gate, yeah, yeah, how to cheese mode every encounter because you know, okay, all right, you're in the sewers.
Um, this has got a lot of more passageways and whatnot.
In this particular case, this is the only passageway you see.
Um, all right, and standing, you head down, and uh, there is Rsolk and his gang, the Dead Rats.
That's the name of the gang, yeah, the dead rats.
I thought it was the rat pack, that's so much better.
You gotta go with that.
Well, I mean, does Vukradin suggest that?
Uh, it sounds like Soma suggested it.
It's a great suggestion, yeah.
I know, but but you're Vukradin, and she's just Soma.
Oh, yeah, so you know, just Soma.
All right, the rat pack it is, it's the dead rats, man.
We need the dead rat pack.
How about she goes?
Like, rat pack is kind of like calling a total choose your next word carefully: the most amazing creature in divine grace, darn tootin.
Um, all right, he goes, uh, he looks at you, he's pleased to see you, but he's also uh a little bit disappointed to discover you an armed expedition has shown up.
And the first words out of his mouth are: found yourself then.
Remember, you'd lost your, but you had been lost.
Oh, Vukradin.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Found yourself.
Well, you're the one who sent us down here.
We had a whole conversation about it.
Yeah, I know.
He's looking at, but you came around, you came around with a few more people.
Well, you didn't expect me to kill all these spiders by myself, did you?
I don't know what I expected.
Anyway, so look, I need you.
So you're going to go clear out the spiders?
I suppose.
All right.
And we never messing with all the trade routes.
Yeah, it's like that.
That those spiders have been blocked.
So the passageway, the passageway, there was a passageway past that location, which had nobody wanted to go down.
And the spiders have taken residence up in a junction that goes down our passageways.
Okay.
So we just need you to go deal with the spiders and come back, give us our money.
We'll give you the money.
He looks at you and he says, 200 gold pieces?
250.
What?
Did you have another party of adventurers that was going to clear out the mouth for you?
He just littered with willing people.
Do you have a lot of leverage here that I wasn't aware of?
250.
We'll see you.
We'll be back soon.
I got a date with the Lord tonight.
What?
We'll be back soon.
All right.
Okay.
Let me get my map.
All right.
So you head down the hallway.
And we fling the familiar ahead just for, you know.
Shits and giggles.
Well, you know, making sure that it spots spiders before we get caught, all that stuff.
Let me just make sure.
Let's see.
Can you guys see?
Can you guys see anything?
Oh, let me just make sure.
So I just realized I haven't used dynamic.
The other person hasn't done very much is gender.
And I forgot to put on explore mode.
That's what I forgot to do.
All right.
Oh, suddenly the map has changed.
Yes, because I was not set up.
I had not.
Okay, now we're back here.
All right.
No, I just was just to show you what I just realized that and everything.
The nice thing about a five-foot passageway is it's a 15-foot.
Oh, it's 15 feet.
And don't pay too much attention to this.
The map, the battle map, is going to be look slightly differently.
Okay.
All right.
I see white.
See graph paper.
What?
We just see graph paper.
Yeah, that's the problem.
First, it was Google Drive.
What the hell?
I just spent like a non-true amount of time drawing this map.
There's nothing.
I know.
That's really effing annoying.
Language?
Yes, Soma.
I'm sorry.
I got to be careful.
We got to use the right language in front of Soma.
All right.
Give me like two seconds to draw.
I literally spent quite a bit of time drawing this map.
All right.
Most of the time, trying to decide what the map would be, so I can do this very quickly.
Yeah, just make it up as you go.
Exactly.
All right, so we'll have to do
okay,
and here let me show you what the
all right.
So, this is that's perfectly fine.
Yes, I know.
So, this is what it kind of is supposed to look like.
And
ah, and my icon, my tokens got lost, which is very annoying.
That's okay.
I have my tokens.
This can be done in a second.
You can always buy more tokens.
Yeah, I know.
We did just say that, right?
Hey, isn't this the room where you meet Withers?
No, not quite.
Did you just say that?
It almost looks like it.
Yeah, you know.
I mean, there's always so many ways to draw a dank dungeon.
Yeah.
All right.
So.
So here are the spiders.
I saw a lot of spiders.
Before we go in.
Hold on, hold on.
Let me just one more thing I have to draw.
So there's this essentially, and then there's the boss spider, which I will put over here because I didn't have time to create an icon.
A load-bearing spider.
Did you say load-bearing?
I hate you.
What?
Because it's like the quintessential, the word that the infernal app uses.
Oh, that.
Yes.
I was used to the joke of, oh, that boss was load-bearing because when you kill him, the dungeon starts to crumble and fall apart.
Let me just put some tocoons.
This predates my, you know, clawed obsession.
I understand.
Okay.
All right.
Nice party.
Except the party isn't all here.
Everybody gets part of inspiration.
Okay.
Vukradin, Valphine, Soma.
And who else?
Brewbarry.
All right.
Okie dokie.
Alrighty.
So just to give you some lay of the land, this is the middle area here, which is full of water.
There is a big boss spider standing over, standing, let's say, clinging on to a web above the ground.
Let me just draw the web here.
Are there like webs all around?
Yeah, I was about to draw that.
What are we looking at for ceiling height here?
25 feet.
Gary, what do you think about me blowing my fourth level?
Gary, are you there?
You're listening.
What do you think about me casting freedom of movement on Brewbarry?
That's great.
It's my only fourth level spell slot.
I have other spell slot, but I wasn't going to use freedom of movement.
Yeah, but with all these webs probably useful for him.
Yeah, so Brewbarry gets freedom of movement, and that's good for one hour.
Mendenhall, your character die.
Why do you keep saying that?
Just Mendenhall, not everybody.
Yes, but we like, we like Mendenhall.
And we start, we're stuck.
Yeah, Dave.
I just said his character died.
Dave is his character.
Good night.
All right.
So, yes, this side has spidery webs on it.
And this side has a control system which can control the water.
And you notice that water is slowly seeping into this area.
Okay.
Well, essentially, this is.
Freedom of movement means that Brewbarry can swim as fast as he can walk.
All right.
The energy over here looks like.
We don't have anything that's for water breathing, right?
No.
And the water is not that deep.
And it's not exactly water.
Well, I mean, you know, there is water substances in it.
Oh, yeah.
All right.
Brewbarry, charge.
No, roll for initiative.
It's got it.
It's been so long.
I know.
Do we know how to roll for initiative?
We got a seven.
Does Brewbarry have advantage on this shift for some reason?
That's what I saw in the roll, but I would have done it wrong.
I think he does for one of his abilities.
Could be.
Yeah.
Cool.
Nifty.
14 for him.
14.
All right.
Did you want to put the stat blocks?
The monsters on with one, two, three, four, five spiders.
What'd you say?
Don't you want to put the yeah, I need to.
I just get the, I just realized I don't have the stat block for these spiders.
26 hit points.
No problem.
AC14.
It's easy peasy.
No.
No, I'm sure.
Hay spiders?
Bay spider?
There's a few more opponents.
Yeah, hold on.
Have they call them Rift Weavers or something?
Yes.
We faced these in the warehouse, right?
You faced them.
We had Rift in Gnomes, didn't we?
No, that was in the counting house.
Yeah, it was in the dwarfish citadel that had been deep.
Yeah, where we got.
Is that where we got Bony?
We got four then.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Armor class 13, hit points 32.
Except, and the big boss is 15 and 95.
Class 13, hit points 32.
Yeah, armor.
And the other one's Armor Class 15 and hit points 95.
Okay.
All right.
Does the boss have a name?
Rift Weaver Prime.
Love it.
The thing about.
The thing they're beginning to realize is they don't really have a personality.
Personality.
They're spiders.
Yeah.
But yeah, but they don't behave like spiders.
They move in packs.
They seem to be particularly interested in particular things.
They're not.
That sounds like a personality to me.
Okay.
Brewbarry, you could probably kill two of these in one round.
Go for it.
I think I.
We need some initiative rolls, though.
Yes.
Initiative.
Plus two on their initiative.
Yeah, let me just make sure that's correct.
Yeah, plus two.
All right.
There should be six of them.
One, two, three, four.
One more.
There's one missing.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
Coffee.
All right.
All righty.
Sort
phase spider three.
Phase spider three.
All right, what does phase spider three do?
By the way, I recommend not going in the room.
Oh, we need a roll-off.
Vukradin against the master 195.
Gotcha.
Sure, except for Brewbarry.
Brewbarry can go in the room and get surrounded.
He will not be in one.
Yeah, I don't think you're going to want to go in the room.
Why is that?
You're controlling Brewbarry, so you decide.
Uh-huh.
But he'll go after me.
So as long as Soma doesn't go in the room.
Spider three.
Charge.
Spider three, right?
All right.
Okay.
So it will attempt to.
I guess Soma is standing at the very opening.
Hey, Soma and Valphine appear to be in front.
You wouldn't have had Brewbarry up front?
Yeah.
I should probably fix that.
I think it'd be Soma and Brewbarry up front.
Soma and Brewbarry.
All right.
So number three attacks.
I'm sorry.
It's a plus four for 15 against, I guess, Brewbarry.
What's Brewbarry's armor class?
Brewbarry's armor class is 15, I think.
17.
I'll fix the tracker.
Okay, because it says 15.
All right.
That is a miss.
Okay.
That's it.
Soma?
Also.
Oh, there's more.
All right.
Layer actions.
No.
A bonus action.
Bonus action.
And he goes over here.
He sort of phases in and out.
That's not going to help.
That's fine.
I mean, whatever.
I mean, I don't know what you're going to do.
Like, yes, you're going to do something amazing.
I'm doing the creatures only have so many thoughts.
Okay.
That's fine.
All right.
Soma.
Do you tell Soma to not rush in or not?
Yeah, don't rush it.
Don't rush it.
All right.
We're flaming spear over here, though.
Sometimes webs on fire.
That's the plan.
Just light everything up.
And also, the sphere is sort of familiar that I can bounce around.
I was freaking wear that.
All right.
So how much damage does the flaming sphere do?
It did seven damage, but it also, you know, sets ablaze things.
And it's a up here on number one.
So I need to.
Sorry, it's been a little while.
I've got to remember how to find the tokens.
State of five-foot radius.
There you go.
Yeah, it'll do.
I can't move that.
There we go.
All right.
Well, it's over there, right?
Yeah, for now.
I mean, next turn I'll move it, but whatever.
All right.
It's over there, presumably setting things on fire, doing some minor damage to number one.
She has a DC save.
What's the save?
DC 15 dexterity.
Ah, makes the saving throw so he doesn't take any gap.
Just take half damage.
Fiddle sticks.
Let me double-check.
Yeah, I think it's half damage.
Half damage, yeah, so he takes three.
Ah, but because he's vulnerable to fire, he takes seven.
Oh, well.
Which I recall from the last time.
That's why you used fire, right?
I wanted to burn all the webs up so we could move around.
Yeah.
That's why the necklace of fireballs.
You don't have the necklace of fireballs.
I know.
Yeah, we gave it to Brewbarry says we could have had the necklace of fireballs.
And then as a bonus action, I think I'm just going to turn into a spider to join the get the freedom of movement.
Well, to also get freedom of movement on this stuff.
Got it.
All right.
That's me.
I'm not charging in yet.
You know, presumably there's a bunch of fire spreading now, so I'm not going to deal with it.
So Soma's just going to wait there patiently.
All right, Valphine.
Well, I've got no more actions.
I've done it a spell and a shift and all like, I'm good.
Movement.
You have movement, but you don't want to use it.
Valphine is sitting here saying, stay the fuck out of the room.
Staying out of the room.
Okay, Valphine's got a plan.
Yeah, I will put the ball of fire in there, then I can control the ball of fire.
That's it.
All right.
Okay.
Valphine.
All right.
You're up, Valphine.
I'm going to cast Doomtide.
What does Doomtide do?
Bad stuff.
Apparently.
24 radius.
All right.
So which three do you want?
Inky fog.
You mean like.
I can get four.
No, they have to be half.
You can get the guy in the corner, you could not get.
He's there.
You can get three.
I can only get three.
Yeah.
But they're large.
Yes, but they're still not, it's still not half.
It's still not half the square.
Like this one is not half.
You'd have to be like, let me see.
Let me just see.
Here.
This is where you'd have to place it.
All right, fine.
If you place it here, you can get four.
Okay.
Wisdom save DC15 for 22 psychic damage.
4d20.
Last.
Okay.
Psychic damage.
Wisdom saving throw.
I'm going to assume they have any resistances.
This definitely doesn't.
Okay.
He chooses.
So the fog is magical darkness and lasts for the duration.
All right, all right.
The prime blows his saving throw, but chooses to pass it using his legendary resistance.
Nice.
Okay.
So it takes 11 psychic.
Yes, everybody else takes full psychic damage.
Okay.
And what else does this do?
On a failed save, you also subtract 1d6 from your saving throws until the end of your next turn.
Got it.
Okay.
And
I think I need to have it go just a little bit like this because it will slowly actually.
Yeah.
Can I do like that?
Yeah, I think you should do it like that.
Okay.
So the main thing is that this gas cloud will slowly waft to the east every turn.
Yeah.
Okay.
We'll slowly waft.
So it's a cloud that wafts to the east.
Is that what I heard?
Yeah.
And it will saving throws down by five.
That creature also makes the save when it moves in, when the sphere moves into its space, when it enters the sphere, or when it ends the turn inside the sphere.
Okay.
So don't end the turn, don't start the turn.
By the way, now I can't see anything, so I won't be able to target any creatures with my attacks.
You could target these guys.
Or this is 20.
Can you see through the fog or just not into it?
Magical darkness.
I mean, you can't.
Well, it's not my turn yet.
We'll see what happens.
You know, concentration.
It's a concentration spell.
So lots of things.
Lots and lots of things happen.
This could still happen.
All right, Brewbarry's up.
Okay.
So, Brewbarry, can he like maybe
see this guy?
You can't see.
If it's darkness, you can't see through it.
Yeah.
No.
No, you, you, you.
Can't see that guy.
Okay, like, all right, he can, but it's three-quarters cover.
How about I do it that way?
So, so let's say you did damage to one, three, and the boss.
Is that right?
I did.
I don't, we originally we were going to do a three, two, and four.
Sorry.
Three, two, and five.
That was the original ones.
Then you moved it.
Okay.
So if we're doing one, three, and the boss, then maybe four is just a little bit outside of it, and then maybe he can see four.
Move the sphere up a little bit.
There you go.
There.
There, then he can see him just fine.
Okay.
All right.
I need to apply the damage here, too.
So it was well.
So one, three, and the boss.
Two and five should have no damage.
Yep.
Correct.
All right.
Okay.
And so then Brewbarry will rage and attack four.
All right.
Can you make him big?
Well, if he gets big, he's in the zone of horror.
Can he not do it from outside of the room?
Oh, he's got incredible reach, doesn't he?
Yeah.
Okay.
He's a man of many talents.
Let me send this to the back order, send two back.
All right.
There you go.
So he's over here.
He can from over here.
I guess he's got enough reach.
So that would be inside the room.
Like from here, he can use his Halberd because he's got enough reach.
So he can attack four from here, right?
Yeah, but he doesn't have to move, is my point.
Yeah.
Okay.
He can attack literally from where he's standing.
He doesn't have to move.
If he has to move, he gets inside of the radius.
That was my only point.
Okay.
So he makes.
That's a miss.
No, no.
I think you rolled.
I think you, yeah, two misses.
Yeah.
He rolled 12 11s.
Confirm you rolled two 11s.
He did.
There are two unique rolls here.
Okay.
Well, that was after all of that amazing effort and platting.
Would you like to use your bardic inspiration?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Or your bless?
How about both?
Okay, so those should be 12 and 14.
Would that say?
So, no, no, it's 13.
It's plus two, right?
Is that what you're getting for the bless?
A bless on the first one would make a 13.
Okay, so that's a hit.
So don't use the bardic inspiration.
Just hit 13.
The second one would also, if you use the bardic inspiration, would also.
So then he uses the bless, use the bless again, or you can only use it once per turn.
That's a good question.
Let's just double-check that.
To every attack roll.
Is it every attack roll?
Yeah, I just checked it.
Okay.
So you didn't have to use the bardic inspiration at all.
So you've now hit on both.
Okay.
So 13 and 15 on four.
So 28 points of damage, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
So it's at four.
Sounds good.
Good.
All right.
Spider number two.
Spider two.
All right.
Spider two cannot see through the magical darkness.
No, he cannot, much to his irritation.
But
he should not walk through the darkness.
No, no, no, no, no.
He's teleporting.
Oh, he's teleporting.
Sure.
Yeah, they're not.
Oh, yeah.
Space spider.
They're not of this world.
Yeah.
Space spiders.
And then he's going to over here.
And he's going to try to grapple Brewbarry with his spidery with his spidery.
Yeah, feel free.
Of all the ones to grapple.
Well, I mean, that's the only one I can grapple.
The rest of you are hiding behind Brewbarry.
Okay.
Brewbarry kind of grew up over me, didn't he?
Yeah, I'm assuming you're kind of like underneath Brewbarry.
Are you a giant spider?
I'm actually a giant spider.
Yeah, anyway.
I don't remember what size it is.
So you can go ahead.
You can try to grapple if you want.
Oh, it's supposed to be large anyway.
Does he roll an athletics check or a strength check?
Well, no, no, it's a two-hit roll.
Hold on.
Okay.
Thank you.
Do you see the note I just put in there, Gary, on freedom of movement?
I freaking remove that.
Okay.
So you're still not visible into the room, right?
Vukradin, where are you?
Like, can you just put yourself on the map?
I am on the map.
No, but like, are you right there?
That is me.
All right.
Okay.
So, yes, they try to grab you.
All right.
So he attempts to grab you with his dry web, particularly dryish web, like glimmers in the dark.
And that's a natural 20.
So he does successfully grab you, but I'm assuming that your ring of your free action makes it so that you are not grabbed.
The freedom of movement automatically escape at the cost of five moves.
It does allow you to escape the restrained condition because it's not a grapple, it's a restrained condition.
Correct.
It does, yeah.
I'm assuming it does.
It costs five movement, but any creature imposing the grappled condition.
No, this is not the grapple condition.
This is the restrained condition.
It says any non-magical restraint.
Fair enough.
This is non-magical.
All right.
This is a spidery web.
That's what he does.
Okay, so then he is restrained at the moment, but can spend five feet of movement to cancel it.
Yes.
So until his turn, he'll be restrained.
And do I not get a grapple check?
No, it's a two-hit.
You can break out of it afterwards.
Oh, okay.
It's not a grapple.
It's an ability.
Rift Weaver.
Spider five?
Spider five.
Okay.
Sorry.
We'll also try to grab Brewbarry and misses.
All right.
Eight arms and can't even hit a jet.
Yeah, broadside at the barn.
And then number one will come over here.
We'll crawl to the surface.
See, let me just make sure I got the whole distance thing right.
Yep.
Comes over here and will attack.
You get an attack, by the way.
No, no, it's his name.
Oh, Brewbarry.
Brewbarry, because he entered the zone of Brewbarry Death.
Right.
15 slashing on one.
All right.
And which killed it?
No, one hasn't been hit.
Oh, it's dead?
Yeah, so it dies on the way there.
All right.
By the way, there's a phantom spider underneath where I'm going.
I just deleted him.
Okay.
All right.
Next.
Aim for Crom?
Yeah.
I was thinking about what should I do?
Did you cast freedom of movement yet?
He did it before the concentration spell.
I did it before the combat started.
And it's a one-hour duration.
It lasts for one hour.
Okay.
So you're good.
All right.
We should do Vukradin's round and stop because it's .
It is indeed.
We're so slow with combat.
Yeah, we are.
We're brusty.
Give us some slack, man.
I'm giving you slack.
I'm just laughing because I kept trying to throw combat at you guys and you kept walking away from it.
Do you want us to go murder hobo?
No, no, no.
No, I don't hate that.
I just think there are consequences to going murder hobo.
Not usually.
Is it possible for me to move here?
Absolutely.
Am I like.
You are out of the zone.
It is.
Okay.
I'm not subject to psychic damage.
No, you're not subject to psychic damage.
Just again, to remind you, the rule is half the square.
Like that.
Does that hit two spiders or three?
Two.
Two for sure.
It has to cover half the token.
So number four has four hit points.
And number two is full.
Okay, so what's the damage?
DC15 deck save for 24 damage.
Okay, the first one's dead.
No, he didn't.
And the second one takes 24 points of damage.
All right, so four is dead, and two takes 24.
Yep.
I'll apply the 24.
Okay.
And then having no longer being threatened, I will retreat.
Yeah, retreat.
He bravely ran away.
Oh, yes.
It's fine.
And we'll stop here.
Alrighty.
Let me insert a road and roll above.
One is dead and four is dead.
Yep.
Yeah.
Yeah, four is dead.
All right, there we go.
Is Boney with us or he's not in the sewers?
I guess we just didn't bring him on.
I wouldn't think he's being in the sewer.
No, that's how you get a horse in and out of the sewers.
Yeah, exactly.
He's not like a Pokeball kind of horse.
Like he's a flesh and blood.
Well, no flesh or blood, but you know, he's a skeletal horse.
I mean, you know, maybe you could collapse him into, you know, bone structure.
He becomes like a jigsaw puzzle every time to reassemble.
Yeah.
Where does the ulna go?
Next to the tibia, is it?
All right, we could do the Rift Weaver's attack so that we at least get it out of the way.
Yeah.
Yeah, leave it at the top of the round.
How is he going to annihilate us?
He's not going to annihilate you.
This was not meant to be a particularly challenging combat.
This was meant to be a.
We're already bonked two of them, right?
Like.
All right.
Okay.
All righty.
So,
all right.
Okay.
So what he does
is he first teleports 40 feet and lands right on top of Vukradin.
You notice that they seem to have a particular obsession for you.
Okay.
They like his music.
He's popular.
That must be it.
So there's no attack property then.
No, no, because it's teleportation.
And then
attack he does.
All right.
He will then attack you.
Okay.
And then he will attempt to attack you.
Good luck.
Like I said, you will attempt.
Make fun of his mother.
You know.
Or whatever.
Your mother only laid one egg, it says.
In spider parlance.
That's a critical.
Nope.
We're going to re-roll.
Oh.
I'll use my reaction.
That's a 13.
That is a miss.
All right.
And now we will end here.
Top initiative.
All right.
And I get to grant somebody advantage.
Who wants advantage?
Brewbarry.
Always.
Take advantage.
And since apparently, since we're having the combat in the tunnel, let me just draw the tunnel.
Oh.
Tunnel.
So then Valphine is not in the tunnel.
Okay.
All right.
There.
I'm kind of putting you guys all here.
Does that mean that Soma is on the ceiling?
Sure.
No, she.
Yeah, Soma's on the ceiling.
All right.
Yes.
Soma's on the ceiling.
The other spider's on the ceiling.
Brewbarry's on the ground.
Is there no ignition of the webs, by the way, for fire?
What?
Was there nothing lit on fire for us?
We haven't gotten.
I figured we would do that.
Okay.
Since it hasn't really affected anything yet.
Yeah, it hasn't really.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, it changes motion for people going in there, but yeah, nobody's gone in.
Yeah, we can do it later.
But just in case you're wondering, the rules on it are like five feet every round.
I see.
Wow, that's slow.
Well, yeah, but the thing also moves 30 feet every round.
So, you know, I'll light my multiple fires for him to track.
Yes.
So I will check the rules and see whether they are anything else.
All right.
Good evening, gentlemen.
It was hard.
Good evening.
All right.
Thank you.
Take care.